{"__cache./api/resource/task/40211/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40211,"taskName":"Designer - Feng Shui","taskDescription":"Evaluate Feng Shui of a Space","xmTaskDescriptor":"Feng Shui Consultants","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":369,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Designer Feng decorator bedroom traditional","textMessagingName":"Feng Shui","rolloverLongDesc":"An oriental approach that looks at how the room's layout \u0026 furnishings affect the flow of energy. The goal is to arrange things so that the room's purpose or mood is supported by the arrangement of doors, windows, angles shapes \u0026 furnishings.","rolloverShortDesc":"Check the \"energy\" patterns of layout \u0026 furnishings.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Evaluate Feng Shui of a Space.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Feng Shui Consultants \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Hire a Feng Shui Decorating Pro","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":3,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Feng Shui Designer","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Designer - Feng Shui","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Feng Shui Designer Need","urlName":"Designer-Feng-Shui","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Feng Shui Consultants - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Reviews \u0026 Costs","searchKeywords":"Designer,Feng,decorator,bedroom,traditional,consultant,space,Shui","emcCategoryOid":-12019,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":518,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Feng Shui Consultants","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40211/":{"taskOID":40211,"originalTaskOID":40211,"setID":518,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4679,"questionDisplayText":"Areas to be Evaluated","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many areas would you like to be evaluated? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4381,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One specific area","answerDisplayText":"One specific area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":848,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"As many as necessary","answerDisplayText":"As many as necessary","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6958,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Whole interior","answerDisplayText":"Whole interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2343,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exterior/landscape","answerDisplayText":"Exterior/landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4681,"questionDisplayText":"Other services","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What types of specific services interest you? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7224,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","answerDisplayText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7225,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","answerDisplayText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7226,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","answerDisplayText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7227,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","answerDisplayText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7228,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","answerDisplayText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7229,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","answerDisplayText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7230,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Advice on selling property quickly","answerDisplayText":"Advice on selling property quickly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7231,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","answerDisplayText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7232,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Five-element color consultation","answerDisplayText":"Five-element color consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4679,"questionDisplayText":"Areas to be Evaluated","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many areas would you like to be evaluated? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4381,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One specific area","answerDisplayText":"One specific area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":848,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"As many as necessary","answerDisplayText":"As many as necessary","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6958,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Whole interior","answerDisplayText":"Whole interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2343,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exterior/landscape","answerDisplayText":"Exterior/landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4381,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One specific area","answerDisplayText":"One specific area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":848,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"As many as necessary","answerDisplayText":"As many as necessary","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6958,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Whole interior","answerDisplayText":"Whole interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2343,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exterior/landscape","answerDisplayText":"Exterior/landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4681,"questionDisplayText":"Other services","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What types of specific services interest you? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7224,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","answerDisplayText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7225,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","answerDisplayText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7226,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","answerDisplayText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7227,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","answerDisplayText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7228,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","answerDisplayText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7229,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","answerDisplayText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7230,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Advice on selling property quickly","answerDisplayText":"Advice on selling property quickly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7231,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","answerDisplayText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7232,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Five-element color consultation","answerDisplayText":"Five-element color consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7224,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","answerDisplayText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7225,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","answerDisplayText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7226,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","answerDisplayText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7227,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","answerDisplayText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7228,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","answerDisplayText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7229,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","answerDisplayText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7230,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Advice on selling property quickly","answerDisplayText":"Advice on selling property quickly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7231,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","answerDisplayText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7232,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Five-element color consultation","answerDisplayText":"Five-element color consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}